(window.webpackJsonp=window.webpackJsonp||[]).push([[0],{17:function(e,t,n){e.exports=n(39)},23:function(e,t,n){},37:function(e,t,n){},39:function(e,t,n){"use strict";n.r(t);var a=n(0),o=n.n(a),s=n(6),r=n.n(s),i=(n(23),n(3)),l=n(11),u=n(12),c=n(13),h=n(16),y=n(14),m=n(15),d=n(1),p=[{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Only",content:"I find meaning in feeling and faith"},{type:"Caribbean",content:"I find meaning in knowledge and experience"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Orinoco",content:"I need constant change and adventure"},{type:"Echoes",content:"I enjoy daily tasks and rhythms"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"May",content:"I'll always believe in something greater than myself."},{type:"Caribbean",content:"I'm skeptical of beliefs that cannot be proven"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Echoes",content:"I lose track of time because it can pass me by"},{type:"Caribbean",content:"I lose track of time because I'm focused on something else."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Storms",content:"Breakups can feel like cleansing."},{type:"If",content:"Breakups are my worst fear."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Anywhere",content:"I have a sense of urgency there is only so much time."},{type:"Only",content:"The passing of time can be healing and revelatory"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"I make new friends fast."},{type:"Storms",content:"People must earn my trust."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Anywhere",content:"I wander to find something."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"I wander for the adventure of it."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Storms",content:"Others think I am cynical."},{type:"May",content:"Others think I am isolated."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Anywhere",content:"Being with someone means you both must change"},{type:"If",content:"Being with someone means devotion to them."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Orinoco",content:"I discover and make my story one day at a time; nothing is written."},{type:"May",content:"I know my story is part of a larger story"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"My passion is sometimes aimless."},{type:"Only",content:"My passion is tempered by my sensitivity"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Echoes",content:"I take things one day at a time."},{type:"May",content:"I want to discover how I fit in the narrative of time."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Anywhere",content:"If I'm traveling somewhere new and get lost, I'll make short explorations in every direction."},{type:"Storms",content:"If I'm traveling somewhere new and get lost, I'll press on in the direction I'm headed."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Only",content:"I am passionate about many things."},{type:"If",content:"I am deeply passionate about only a few things"}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Caribbean",content:"I find beauty is in the details."},{type:"Wild",content:"I'll endure a lot for a moment of beauty."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"May",content:"Others value that I'm true to my word."},{type:"Only",content:"Others value my realistic expectations."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Storms",content:"Sometimes I'm unapproachable because I'm hard to understand."},{type:"Caribbean",content:"Sometimes I'm unapproachable because I'm too caught up in what I'm doing."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"If",content:"I get caught up in dreams."},{type:"Echoes",content:"I get caugt up in the present moment."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Storms",content:"Hardship will come to everyone at some point."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"I can avoid pain if I keep moving."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"If",content:"I want to find and be with my one love."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"There's so much out there, I can't settle down now."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Echoes",content:"I can be predictable."},{type:"Anywhere",content:"I am unpredictable."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"Pleasure and hardship are part of life, so fully living means encountering both."},{type:"May",content:"Hope and despair are wrought in our destiny."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"May",content:"Even in my darkest moments, I trust in a larger meaning."},{type:"Anywhere",content:"I worry sometimes that the world is meaningless."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Only",content:"I question myself."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"I believe in my ability."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"If",content:"Intimacy fulfills me."},{type:"May",content:"I'll always have some sense of loneliness."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Only",content:"When uncomfortable, I become self-conscious and uncertain."},{type:"Echoes",content:"When uncomfortable, I am patient and let things unfold."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Caribbean",content:"I am methodical in my work."},{type:"Anywhere",content:"I wander from task to task, but my work gets done."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"Today, this moment, is where my focus lies."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"I'm always looking to the horizon."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"If",content:"Romance comes naturally to me."},{type:"Caribbean",content:"Relationships require work and attentiveness."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"I marvel at everyday occurences."},{type:"Anywhere",content:"I wonder if there's more significance to each day."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Echoes",content:"I am usually calm and steady."},{type:"Storms",content:"I am often moody."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Wild",content:"I'm drawn to fellow adventurers."},{type:"If",content:"I'm drawn to those who care for me."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Only",content:"It is hard to know somebody; we all have a limited perspective."},{type:"Storms",content:"I can discern a lot about someone in a moment."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Caribbean",content:"When faced with problems, I look to data or the past."},{type:"Orinoco",content:"When faced with problems, I look to my own ability."}]},{question:"Please select one:",answers:[{type:"Echoes",content:"I welcome new experiences"},{type:"Wild",content:"I seek out new experiences"}]}],w=n(4);var f=function(e){return o.a.createElement("h2",{className:"question"},e.content)};var g=function(e){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"questionCount"},"Question ",o.a.createElement("span",null,e.counter)," of ",o.a.createElement("span",null,e.total))};var v=function(e){return o.a.createElement("li",{className:"answerOption"},o.a.createElement("input",{type:"radio",className:"radioCustomButton",name:"radioGroup",checked:e.answerType===e.answer,id:e.answerType,value:e.answerType,disabled:e.answer,onChange:e.onAnswerSelected}),o.a.createElement("label",{className:"radioCustomLabel",htmlFor:e.answerType},e.answerContent))};var I=function(e){return o.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("div",null,o.a.createElement(g,{key:e.questionId+"count",counter:e.questionId,total:e.questionTotal}),o.a.createElement(f,{key:e.questionId,content:e.question}),o.a.createElement("ul",{className:"answerOptions"},e.answerOptions.map(function(t){return o.a.createElement(v,{key:t.content,answerContent:t.content,answerType:t.type,answer:e.answer,questionId:e.questionId,onAnswerSelected:e.onAnswerSelected})}))))},k=[{slug:"Only",full:"Only Time",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Caribbean",full:"Caribbean Blue",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Orinoco",full:"Orinoco Flow (Sail Away)",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Echoes",full:"Echoes in Rain",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Storms",full:"Storms in Africa (Part II)",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"If",full:"If I Could Be Where You Are",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Wild",full:"Wild Child",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"Anywhere",full:"Anywhere Is",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."},{slug:"May",full:"May It Be",description:"It looks so good, I might as well not stop. Clouds are free. They just float around the sky all day and have fun. Let your heart take you to wherever you want to be. Mountains are so simple, they're hard. Anyone can paint.Work on one thing at a time. Don't get carried away - we have plenty of time. There isn't a rule. You just practice and find out which way works best for you. Imagination is the key to painting. All you have to learn here is how to have fun."}];var b=function(e){var t=k.find(function(t){return t.slug===e.option});return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-6 mb-4"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"card"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"card-body"},o.a.createElement("h3",{className:"card-title"},t.full),o.a.createElement("p",{className:"card-text"},t.description))))};var q=function(e){var t=e.quizResult,n=e.quizWings;return t.length>1&&(n.length=0),o.a.createElement(w.CSSTransitionGroup,{className:"result",component:"div",transitionName:"fade",transitionEnterTimeout:800,transitionLeaveTimeout:500,transitionAppear:!0,transitionAppearTimeout:500},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"row pt-4 justify-content-center"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12 mb-2"},t.length>1?o.a.createElement("div",null,"Your Enyagram is as a kite blown in two directions. To determine which wind will guide you best, follow these steps:"," ",o.a.createElement("ol",null,o.a.createElement("li",null,"Read the descriptions and choose the best fit."),o.a.createElement("li",null,"Listen to each song and choose the one that resonates on a spiritual level."),o.a.createElement("li",null,"Listen to what secrets the wind might tell and and trust her.")),"And take heart! The other option is still your wing so let the winds of your results ever lift you up."):"Your Enyagram results:"),t.map(function(e,t){return o.a.createElement(b,{key:t,option:e})}),o.a.createElement("div",{className:"col-sm-12 mb-2"},t.length>1?"":"Your Enyagram Wings"),n.map(function(e,t){return o.a.createElement(b,{key:t,option:e})})))},E=(n(37),function(e){function t(e){var n;return Object(u.a)(this,t),(n=Object(h.a)(this,Object(y.a)(t).call(this,e))).state={counter:0,questionId:1,question:"",answerOptions:[],answer:"",answersCount:{May:0,Echoes:0,Storms:0,Only:0,Caribbean:0,If:0,Wild:0,Anywhere:0,Orinoco:0},result:"",wings:""},n.handleAnswerSelected=n.handleAnswerSelected.bind(Object(d.a)(Object(d.a)(n))),n}return Object(m.a)(t,e),Object(c.a)(t,[{key:"componentWillMount",value:function(){var e=this,t=p.map(function(t){return e.shuffleArray(t.answers)});this.setState({question:p[0].question,answerOptions:t[0]})}},{key:"shuffleArray",value:function(e){for(var t,n,a=e.length;0!==a;)n=Math.floor(Math.random()*a),t=e[a-=1],e[a]=e[n],e[n]=t;return e}},{key:"handleAnswerSelected",value:function(e){var t=this;this.setUserAnswer(e.currentTarget.value),this.state.questionId<p.length?setTimeout(function(){return t.setNextQuestion()},300):setTimeout(function(){return t.setResults(t.getResults(),t.getWings())},300)}},{key:"setUserAnswer",value:function(e){this.setState(function(t,n){return{answersCount:Object(l.a)({},t.answersCount,Object(i.a)({},e,t.answersCount[e]+1)),answer:e}})}},{key:"setNextQuestion",value:function(){var e=this.state.counter+1,t=this.state.questionId+1;this.setState({counter:e,questionId:t,question:p[e].question,answerOptions:p[e].answers,answer:""})}},{key:"getResults",value:function(){var e=this.state.answersCount,t=Object.keys(e),n=t.map(function(t){return e[t]}),a=Math.max.apply(null,n);return t.filter(function(t){return e[t]===a})}},{key:"getWings",value:function(){var e=this.state.answersCount,t=Object.keys(e),n=t.map(function(t){return e[t]}),a=Math.max.apply(null,n);n.splice(n.indexOf(a),1);var o=Math.max.apply(null,n);return t.filter(function(t){return e[t]===o})}},{key:"setResults",value:function(e,t){e.length>=1?(this.setState({result:e}),this.setState({wings:t})):this.setState({result:"Undetermined"})}},{key:"renderQuiz",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(I,{answer:this.state.answer,answerOptions:this.state.answerOptions,questionId:this.state.questionId,question:this.state.question,questionTotal:p.length,onAnswerSelected:this.handleAnswerSelected})}},{key:"renderResult",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(q,{quizResult:this.getResults(),quizWings:this.getWings()})}},{key:"oldRenderResult",value:function(){return o.a.createElement(q,{quizResult:this.state.result})}},{key:"render",value:function(){return o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App"},o.a.createElement("div",{className:"App-header"},o.a.createElement("h2",null,"The Enyagram")),this.state.result?this.renderResult():this.renderQuiz())}}]),t}(a.Component));Boolean("localhost"===window.location.hostname||"[::1]"===window.location.hostname||window.location.hostname.match(/^127(?:\.(?:25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9]|[01]?[0-9][0-9]?)){3}$/));r.a.render(o.a.createElement(E,null),document.getElementById("root")),"serviceWorker"in navigator&&navigator.serviceWorker.ready.then(function(e){e.unregister()})}},[[17,2,1]]]);
//# sourceMappingURL=main.f708c8b6.chunk.js.map